forestholidays.co.uk 2006-02-06

# Privacy Policy | Forest Holidays

**PRIVACY POLICY**

  This page explains how Forest Holidays uses any information you give to us through our website, and the ways in which we protect your privacy.  

  **The Data Protection Act**    
Forest Holidays is part of the Forestry Commission, which is a data controller under the Data Protection Act. Under the Act, we have a legal duty to protect any information we collect from you. We safeguard your data, and keep strict security standards to prevent any unauthorised access to it. We do not pass on your details to any third party or other government department unless you give us permission to do so. 

  **What information do we collect?**    
We collect different kinds of information from visitors to our website:   
‘contact us’ e-mails    
cabin and campsites bookings by e-mail   
brochures requests   
and site usage information from log files 

  **Contact Us**    
You can send us your feedback or ask us questions directly through the website or by e-mail, post or phone. If you use the website ‘contact us’ options you do not need to give any personal information unless you wish a response from us. We do not pass on any of your personal information outside our organisation when dealing with your enquiry. We will not use any information you supply for any other purpose without first seeking your permission. Where your details are held in our tracking system these are archived after we have dealt with your enquiry and deleted after 5 years.  

  **Cabin and Campsite Bookings**    
We will record your information for the purpose of processing your booking, and for contacting you regarding your booking. We will not pass your information on to any third party without your prior permission. We will not send you promotional or other material with your prior permission.  

  All pages handling bookings and processing user data including credit/debit card details are inside the secure section of the website. These details will be kept for 5 years. 

  **Calls to our brochure request lines**    
The information you supply to us in telephone contacts may be logged within a database to help us respond to, and track, your request. We will not use any information you supply for any other purpose without your permission. Our system archives your message after it has been dealt with, and deletes them after 5 years.  

  **Brochure requests on-line**    
We will record your personal contact details to be able to respond to you, and track the progress of your request. If you use the brochure request function on the website the minimum personal information required from you is an e-mail address or telephone contact number. We do not pass on any of your personal information outside our organisation when dealing with your enquiry, unless you have given us permission to do so. We will not use any information you supply for any other purpose without your permission. 

  If your enquiry is logged our system archives your message after it has been dealt with, and deletes it after 5 years. 

  **Registration Details**    
If you register an interest in receiving regular updates via e-mail or post your details will be kept indefinitely. You have the option to check the details supplied by you, to update these details, or to remove your name from any mailing lists by contacting us. The details you supply will only be used for the purpose stated when the information was collected unless you give us permission for other uses (for example to be included in mailing lists). 

  **Cookies and Log Files**    
Cookies are pieces of data that can be automatically created on your computer when you visit a website. We do not use cookies on our website.  

  Log files allow us to record, for statistical purposes visitors' use of the site, which we use to make changes to the layout of the site and to the information in it, based on the way that visitors move around it. Log files do not contain any personal information about you or information about which other sites you have visited.  

  **Links to other sites**    
www.forestholidays.co.uk contains links to the Forestry Commission website. This privacy policy applies only to our site, so you should always be aware when you are moving to another site, which collects personal information to read their privacy statement.  

  **Access to your information and contacting us**    
You can change your registration information by contacting us. If you wish to see our records of any correspondence you have sent to us, or if you have a query or complaint about this privacy policy or about the site, you can contact us by e-mail, phone or post:   
e-mail: fe.holidays@forestry.gsi.gov.uk 

    Phone: 0131 314 6505   
Post: Marketing Manager   
Forest Holidays   
231 Corstorphine Road   
Edinburgh   
EH12 7AT 

  If this privacy policy changes in any way, we will place an updated version on this page. Regularly reviewing this page ensures you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances, if any, we will share it with other parties. 

  **October 2003**
